UNESCO Second Canadian Archaeological Expedition to Carthage Records MS210
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Carthage Site Maps, 1913 -- 1998; 1978 -- 1998; MS210.005; 7.75 Linear Feet
  - Published Maps, 1913 -- 1998; 1978 -- 1998; MS210.005.001; 7.75 Linear Feet
    - Carthage Theodosian Wall, Northern Sector Canadian Excavation - Main Site 2CC1 and 2CC2 - Final State, 1976 -- 1986; MS210.005.001.00036 (Box data_value_missing_97cfa01f138be565b59549700ce0186c)
    - Carthage Theodosian Wall, Northern Sector Canadian Excavation - Main Site 2CC1 and 2CC2 - Final State, 1976 -- 1986; MS210.005.001.00037 (Box data_value_missing_97cfa01f138be565b59549700ce0186c)
    - Carthage Northern Sector Canadian Excavation - Main Site 2CC1 and 2CC2 - Final State, 1976 -- 1986; MS210.005.001.00038 (Box data_value_missing_97cfa01f138be565b59549700ce0186c)
    - Carthage Northern Sector Canadian Excavations Topography map, 1976 -- 1978; MS210.005.001.00039 (Box data_value_missing_97cfa01f138be565b59549700ce0186c)
    - Carthage Theodosian Wall, Northern Sector Main Site 2CC1 and 2CC2 - Final State, 1976 -- 1986; MS210.005.001.00040 (Box data_value_missing_10890b8dfc8b9d0e72ba6dde5bcf6fce)
    - Carthage Theodosian Wall, Northern Sector Main Site 2CC1 and 2CC2 - Final State, 1976 -- 1986; MS210.005.001.00041 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 1)
    - Carthage Theodosian Wall, Northern Sector Main Site 2CC1 and 2CC2 - Final State, 1976 -- 1986; MS210.005.001.00042 (Box Large Map Case 1 Drawer 9)
    - Carthage Theodosian Wall, Northern Sector Main Site 2CC1 and 2CC2 - Final State (with grid), 1976 -- 1986; MS210.005.001.00043 (Box data_value_missing_97cfa01f138be565b59549700ce0186c)
    - Carthage Theodosian Wall, Northern Sector Main Site 2CC1 and 2CC2 - Final State (with grid), 1976 -- 1986; MS210.005.001.00044 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 1)
    - Carthage Theodosian Wall, Northern Sector Main Site 2CC1 and 2CC2 - Final State, 1976 -- 1986; MS210.005.001.00045 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 1)
    - Carthage Theodosian Wall, Northern Sector Main Site 2CC1 and 2CC2 - Final State, 1976 -- 1986; MS210.005.001.00046 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 2)
    - Carthage Theodosian Wall, Northern Sector Main Site 2CC1 and 2CC2 - Final State, 1976 -- 1986; MS210.005.001.00047 (Box Small Map Case 1 Drawer 1)
    - Bath Complex State Plan Level 1, 1990; MS210.005.001.00048 (Box Large Map Case 1 Drawer 9)
    - Bath Complex State Plan Level 2, 1990; MS210.005.001.00049 (Box Large Map Case 1 Drawer 9)
    - Bath Complex State Plan Level 3, 1990; MS210.005.001.00050 (Box Large Map Case 1 Drawer 9)
    - Carthage Theodosian Wall, Northern Sector Canadian Excavations 1976-1986, continued by Trinity 1990-1992, 1976 -- 1992; MS210.005.001.00051 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 1)
    - Carthage Theodosian Wall, Northern Sector Canadian Excavations 1976-1986, continued by Trinity 1990-1992 in relation to street grid, 1976 -- 1992; MS210.005.001.00052 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 1)
    - Carthage Theodosian Wall, Northern Sector Canadian Excavations 1976-1986, continued by Trinity 1990-1992 in relation to street grid, 1976 -- 1992; MS210.005.001.00053 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 1)
    - Carthage Theodosian Wall, Northern Sector Canadian Excavations 1976-1986, continued by Trinity 1990-1992 in relation to street grid, 1976 -- 1992; MS210.005.001.00054 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 1)
    - Carthage Theodosian Wall, Northern Sector Canadian Excavation - Main Site 2CC1 and 2CC2 - Final State (with grid), 1976 -- 1986; MS210.005.001.00055 (Box data_value_missing_97cfa01f138be565b59549700ce0186c)
    - Carthage Theodosian Wall, Northern Sector Main Site 2CC1 and 2CC2 - Final State (with tracing), 1976 -- 1986; MS210.005.001.00056 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 2)
    - Carthage Hill of the Odeon, Archaeological Trenches, 1994 -- 1997; MS210.005.001.00057 (Box 1)
    - Carthage Hill of the Odeon, Archaeological Trenches, 1994 -- 1997; MS210.005.001.00058 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 2)
    - Carthage Hill of the Odeon, trenches with excavation and topography, 1994 -- 1997; MS210.005.001.00059 (Box 1)
    - Carthage Hill of the Odeon, trenches with excavation and topography, 1994 -- 1997; MS210.005.001.00060 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 2)
    - Carthage Northern Sector Canadian Excavations Main Site - with highlights and edits, MS210.005.001.00061 (Box Large Map Case 1 Drawer 9)
    - Carthage Northern Sector Canadian Excavations Main Site, MS210.005.001.00062 (Box data_value_missing_10890b8dfc8b9d0e72ba6dde5bcf6fce)
    - Carthage Hill of the Odeon, trenches with excavation and topography and notes, 1976 -- 1998; MS210.005.001.00063 (Box data_value_missing_97cfa01f138be565b59549700ce0186c)
    - Carthage Theodosian Wall part 1, 1976 -- 1986; MS210.005.001.00064 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 2)
    - Carthage Theodosian Wall part 1, 1976 -- 1986; MS210.005.001.00065 (Box data_value_missing_97cfa01f138be565b59549700ce0186c)
    - Carthage Theodosian Wall part 2, 1976 -- 1986; MS210.005.001.00066 (Box data_value_missing_97cfa01f138be565b59549700ce0186c)
    - Carthage Theodosian Wall part 2, 1976 -- 1986; MS210.005.001.00067 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 2)
    - Carthage Theodosian Wall part 3, 1976 -- 1986; MS210.005.001.00068 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 2)
    - Carthage Theodosian Wall part 3, 1976 -- 1986; MS210.005.001.00069 (Box data_value_missing_97cfa01f138be565b59549700ce0186c)
    - Carthage Northern Sector Canadian Excavations Main Site - 2CC1, 2CC2, 2CC2A with grid, 1976 -- 1986; MS210.005.001.00070 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 1)
    - Carthage Northern Sector Canadian Excavations Main Site - 2CC1, 2CC2, 2CC2A with grid, 1976 -- 1986; MS210.005.001.00071 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 1)
    - Carthage Theodosian Wall part 1, 1976 -- 1986; MS210.005.001.00072 (Box data_value_missing_97cfa01f138be565b59549700ce0186c)
    - Carthage Theodosian Wall part 2, 1976 -- 1986; MS210.005.001.00073 (Box data_value_missing_97cfa01f138be565b59549700ce0186c)
    - Carthage Theodosian Wall part 3, 1976 -- 1986; MS210.005.001.00074 (Box data_value_missing_97cfa01f138be565b59549700ce0186c)
    - Carthage Northern Sector Canadian Excavations Main Site, 1976 -- 1986; MS210.005.001.00075 (Box data_value_missing_97cfa01f138be565b59549700ce0186c)
    - Carthage Northern Sector Canadian Excavations Main Site, 1976 -- 1986; MS210.005.001.00076 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 1)
    - Carthage Northern Sector Canadian Excavations Main Site, 1976 -- 1986; MS210.005.001.00077 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 1)
    - Carthage Northern Sector Canadian Excavations - Excavations in Relation to Theoretical Street Grid, 1976 -- 1986; MS210.005.001.00078 (Box data_value_missing_97cfa01f138be565b59549700ce0186c)
    - 2CC4, 2CC7, survey (emw), 1998; MS210.005.001.00079 (Box data_value_missing_97cfa01f138be565b59549700ce0186c)
    - Carthage topography of Main site and Odeon Hill, with street grid, 1992 -- 1998; MS210.005.001.00080 (Box Small Map Case 1 Drawer 1)
    - La Marasa Megara map by G. Larissiere Del., MS210.005.001.00081 (Box Small Map Case 1 Drawer 1)
    - The Odeon Hill at Carthage (computer model), 1955 -- 1992; MS210.005.001.00082 (Box data_value_missing_97cfa01f138be565b59549700ce0186c)
    - Carthage Northern Sector Canadian Excavations Main Site - 2CC1, 2CC2, 2CC2A with grid and notes, 1976 -- 1986; MS210.005.001.00083 (Box Small Map Case 1 Drawer 1)
    - Odeon Hill, 1992 -- 1998; MS210.005.001.00084 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 2)
    - Odeon Hill, 1992 -- 1998; MS210.005.001.00085 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 2)
    - Odeon Hill, 1992 -- 1998; MS210.005.001.00086 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 1)
    - Carthage Hill of the Odeon, Surveyed Area & Control Points, University of Waterloo/Trinity University, 1992 -- 1998; MS210.005.001.00087 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 1)
    - Carthage Hill of the Odeon, The Roman Odeon - Analysis, 1992 -- 1998; MS210.005.001.00088 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 1)
    - Carthage Hill of the Odeon, The Roman Odeon - Analysis, 1992 -- 1998; MS210.005.001.00089 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 1)
    - Odeon Hill topography, 1992 -- 1998; MS210.005.001.00090 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 1)
    - Odeon Hill Analysis, 1992 -- 1998; MS210.005.001.00091 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 1)
    - Analytical Maps 1:7500, 1998; MS210.005.001.00092 (Box data_value_missing_97cfa01f138be565b59549700ce0186c)
      Joys project
    - Labeled SE sector of Odeon block, 1992 -- 1998; MS210.005.001.00093 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 1)
    - Labeled sector of Odeon block, 1992 -- 1998; MS210.005.001.00094 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 1)
    - Odeon Plan packet, 1976 -- 1998; MS210.005.001.00095 (Box data_value_missing_97cfa01f138be565b59549700ce0186c)
    - Aerial computer model of Odeon Hill, MS210.005.001.00096 (Box data_value_missing_97cfa01f138be565b59549700ce0186c)
    - Aerial computer model of Odeon Hill, MS210.005.001.00097 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 1)
    - Aerial computer model of Odeon Hill, MS210.005.001.00098 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 1)
    - Aerial computer model of Odeon Hill, MS210.005.001.00099 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 1)
    - Aerial computer model of a section of Odeon Hill, MS210.005.001.00100 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 1)
    - Aerial computer model of a section of Odeon Hill, MS210.005.001.00101 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 1)
    - Aerial computer model of Odeon Hill and Northern Sector, MS210.005.001.00102 (Box data_value_missing_97cfa01f138be565b59549700ce0186c)
    - Aerial topography of Carthage Odeon Hill, MS210.005.001.00103 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 1)
    - Carthage topograhy of Odeon Hill area with street grid, MS210.005.001.00104 (Box Small Map Case 1 Drawer 1)
    - Odeon Hil topography with unnamed street grid, MS210.005.001.00105 (Box data_value_missing_87fbd8863af5c57c69c63481083f09a9)
    - Odeon Hil topography with named street grid, MS210.005.001.00106 (Box data_value_missing_87fbd8863af5c57c69c63481083f09a9)
    - Carthage Hill of the Odeon, Surveyed Area & Control Points, University of Waterloo/Trinity University, 1992 -- 1998; MS210.005.001.00107 (Box 1)
    - Carthage Hill of the Odeon, The Roman Odeon - Analysis, 1992 -- 1998; MS210.005.001.00108 (Box 1)
    - Odeon Hill area map, 1992 -- 1998; MS210.005.001.00109 (Box 1)
    - La Marasa Megara map by G. Larissiere Del., MS210.005.001.00110 (Box data_value_missing_dc7ace542b41f32a9f14d9cbd2de2f1e)
    - 2CC Squares, MS210.005.001.00111 (Box data_value_missing_97cfa01f138be565b59549700ce0186c)
  - Stratigraphic Maps, 1979 -- 1994; MS210.005.002; 4.8 Linear Feet
    This series contains stratigraphic maps and drawings from 1979-1994, of sections from the UNESCO's Second Canadian Archaeological dig at the 2CC Northern Sector of the Theodosian wall. These records show the evolution of the dig locations as trenches were further uncovered and evaluated.
    This series is arranged roughly chronologically by date.
    - Building A, MSG June/ Sept scale 1:20, 1982; MS210.005.002.00001 (Box data_value_missing_10890b8dfc8b9d0e72ba6dde5bcf6fce)
    - Building A, MSG June/ Sept scale 1:20, 1982; MS210.005.002.00002 (Box data_value_missing_10890b8dfc8b9d0e72ba6dde5bcf6fce)
    - Building A, MSG map, 1982; MS210.005.002.00003 (Box data_value_missing_dc7ace542b41f32a9f14d9cbd2de2f1e)
    - Stratigraphic section, west of Building A 2CC1 and 2, 1982 -- 1983; MS210.005.002.00004 (Box data_value_missing_dc7ace542b41f32a9f14d9cbd2de2f1e)
    - Stratigraphic drawing of cistern wall and archway, MS210.005.002.00005 (Box data_value_missing_97cfa01f138be565b59549700ce0186c)
    - Stratigraphic drawing of wall, MS210.005.002.00006 (Box data_value_missing_97cfa01f138be565b59549700ce0186c)
    - Stratigraphic drawing of 2CC1/2CC2 J, facing block, robber trench, plaster edge and stone wall, MS210.005.002.00007 (Box data_value_missing_10890b8dfc8b9d0e72ba6dde5bcf6fce)
    - Large stratigraphic drawing on graph paper, MS210.005.002.00008 (Box Large Map Case 1 Drawer 9)
    - Stratigraphic drawing of parallel wall in IG, MS210.005.002.00009 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 1)
    - 2F/1J/1H, 1979 -- 1994; MS210.005.002.00010 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 2)
    - 1N4, 1979 -- 1983; MS210.005.002.00011 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 1)
    - Corridor, 1979; MS210.005.002.00012 (Box data_value_missing_97cfa01f138be565b59549700ce0186c)
    - 1N, 1979 -- 1983; MS210.005.002.00013 (Box data_value_missing_97cfa01f138be565b59549700ce0186c)
    - 1U, 1983; MS210.005.002.00014 (Box data_value_missing_97cfa01f138be565b59549700ce0186c)
    - M.S.G plans and sections, 1982 -- 1985; MS210.005.002.00015 (Box data_value_missing_97cfa01f138be565b59549700ce0186c)
    - 1V, 1979 -- 1988; MS210.005.002.00016 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 1)
    - 2CC - Elevations, 1980 -- 1983; MS210.005.002.00017 (Box data_value_missing_97cfa01f138be565b59549700ce0186c)
    - 2A, 2B, 1983 -- 1988; MS210.005.002.00018 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 1)
    - Stratigraphic drawing of wall, MS210.005.002.00019 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 1)
    - Stratigraphic drawings of walls, MS210.005.002.00020 (Box data_value_missing_97cfa01f138be565b59549700ce0186c)
    - Stratigraphic drawing of wall, MS210.005.002.00021 (Box data_value_missing_97cfa01f138be565b59549700ce0186c)
    - Stratigraphic drawing of wall, MS210.005.002.00022 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 1)
    - Stratigraphic drawing of wall, MS210.005.002.00023 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 1)
    - Stratigraphic drawing of wall, MS210.005.002.00024 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 1)
    - Stratigraphic drawing of wall, MS210.005.002.00025 (Box data_value_missing_97cfa01f138be565b59549700ce0186c)
    - Stratigraphic drawing of wall, MS210.005.002.00026 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 1)
    - Stratigraphic drawing of wall, MS210.005.002.00027 (Box data_value_missing_97cfa01f138be565b59549700ce0186c)
    - Stratigraphic drawing of wall in 2CC1, MS210.005.002.00028 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 1)
    - Stratigraphic drawing of wall, MS210.005.002.00029 (Box data_value_missing_97cfa01f138be565b59549700ce0186c)
    - Stratigraphic drawing of wall, MS210.005.002.00030 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 1)
    - Stratigraphic drawing of wall, MS210.005.002.00031 (Box data_value_missing_97cfa01f138be565b59549700ce0186c)
    - Stratigraphic drawing of wall, MS210.005.002.00032 (Box data_value_missing_97cfa01f138be565b59549700ce0186c)
    - Stratigraphic drawing of wall, MS210.005.002.00033 (Box data_value_missing_97cfa01f138be565b59549700ce0186c)
    - Stratigraphic drawing of cistern wall, MS210.005.002.00034 (Box data_value_missing_dc7ace542b41f32a9f14d9cbd2de2f1e)
    - Labeled stratigraphic drwaing of section west of Building A, MS210.005.002.00035 (Box data_value_missing_dc7ace542b41f32a9f14d9cbd2de2f1e)
    - Unlabeled stratigraphic drawing of wall, MS210.005.002.00036 (Box data_value_missing_dc7ace542b41f32a9f14d9cbd2de2f1e)
    - 1N4 wall section, MS210.005.002.00037 (Box data_value_missing_dc7ace542b41f32a9f14d9cbd2de2f1e)
    - 1N4 wall section, MS210.005.002.00038 (Box data_value_missing_dc7ace542b41f32a9f14d9cbd2de2f1e)
    - Unlabeled Stratigraphic drawing of wall, MS210.005.002.00039 (Box data_value_missing_dc7ace542b41f32a9f14d9cbd2de2f1e)
    - Unlabeled Stratigraphic drawing of wall, MS210.005.002.00040 (Box data_value_missing_dc7ace542b41f32a9f14d9cbd2de2f1e)
    - Unlabeled Stratigraphic drawing of wall, MS210.005.002.00041 (Box data_value_missing_dc7ace542b41f32a9f14d9cbd2de2f1e)
    - Unlabeled Stratigraphic drawing of wall, MS210.005.002.00042 (Box data_value_missing_dc7ace542b41f32a9f14d9cbd2de2f1e)
    - Stratigraphic drawing of 2CC1/2CC2 J, facing block, robber trench, plaster edge and stone wall, MS210.005.002.00043 (Box data_value_missing_dc7ace542b41f32a9f14d9cbd2de2f1e)
    - Unlabeled Stratigraphic drawing of wall, MS210.005.002.00044 (Box data_value_missing_dc7ace542b41f32a9f14d9cbd2de2f1e)
    - Unlabeled Stratigraphic drawing of wall, MS210.005.002.00045 (Box data_value_missing_dc7ace542b41f32a9f14d9cbd2de2f1e)
    - Unlabeled Stratigraphic drawing of wall, MS210.005.002.00046 (Box data_value_missing_dc7ace542b41f32a9f14d9cbd2de2f1e)
    - Alain Erdmer's version of Building A, MS210.005.002.00047 (Box data_value_missing_dc7ace542b41f32a9f14d9cbd2de2f1e)
    - Stratigraphic line map centered in 1H, MS210.005.002.00048 (Box data_value_missing_87fbd8863af5c57c69c63481083f09a9)
    - Stratigraphic line map centered in 2F, MS210.005.002.00049 (Box data_value_missing_87fbd8863af5c57c69c63481083f09a9)
    - Building A, MSG map, 1982; MS210.005.002.00050 (Box Small Map Case 1 Drawer 1)
    - Stratigraphic section, west of Building A 2CC1 and 2, 1982 -- 1983; MS210.005.002.00051 (Box Small Map Case 1 Drawer 1)
    - Stratigraphic drawing of 2CC1/2CC2 J, facing block, robber trench, plaster edge and stone wall, MS210.005.002.00052 (Box data_value_missing_97cfa01f138be565b59549700ce0186c)
    - Stratigraphic section, west of Building A 2CC1 and 2, 1982 -- 1983; MS210.005.002.00053 (Box Small Map Case 1 Drawer 1)
- Carthage Site Drawings, 1979 -- 1983; MS210.006; 5.35 Linear Feet
  This series contains drawings from 1979-1983, of sections UNESCO's Second Canadian Archaeological dig at the 2CC Northern Sector of the Theodosian wall and the archaeological dig sponsored by Trinity University at the Hill of Odeon. They include tracings from mosaics discovered at the sites.
  - Tracing of MSG mosaic, MS210.006.00001 (Box data_value_missing_89dee03018a7302e2b9eb234f7288880)
  - Drawing by KMBaker in plastic, 1982; MS210.006.00002 (Box Small Map Case 1 Drawer 1)
  - Kathleen's Drawings, 1982; MS210.006.00003 (Box data_value_missing_97cfa01f138be565b59549700ce0186c)
  - P.M Anselm drawings, unlabeled close up sections of Main Site, 1983; MS210.006.00004 (Box data_value_missing_10890b8dfc8b9d0e72ba6dde5bcf6fce)
  - P.M Anselm drawings, unlabeled close up sections of Main Site, 1983; MS210.006.00005 (Box data_value_missing_10890b8dfc8b9d0e72ba6dde5bcf6fce)
  - P.M Anselm drawing, untitled, 1983; MS210.006.00006 (Box data_value_missing_dc7ace542b41f32a9f14d9cbd2de2f1e)
  - P.M Anselm "Respexit", 1983; MS210.006.00007 (Box data_value_missing_97cfa01f138be565b59549700ce0186c)
  - P.M Anselm "Respexit", 1983; MS210.006.00008 (Box Small Map Case 1 Drawer 1)
  - Unlabeled drawing of section of Northern Sector Excavations, MS210.006.00009 (Box data_value_missing_10890b8dfc8b9d0e72ba6dde5bcf6fce)
  - Unlabeled drawing of large section of Northern Sector Excavations, MS210.006.00010 (Box data_value_missing_10890b8dfc8b9d0e72ba6dde5bcf6fce)
  - Drawing of 2CC1 and 2 sections with labeled grid, MS210.006.00011 (Box data_value_missing_10890b8dfc8b9d0e72ba6dde5bcf6fce)
  - Unlabeled drawing of section of Northern Sector Excavations, MS210.006.00012 (Box data_value_missing_10890b8dfc8b9d0e72ba6dde5bcf6fce)
  - Unlabeled drawing and blue print of section of Northern Sector Excavations, MS210.006.00013 (Box data_value_missing_10890b8dfc8b9d0e72ba6dde5bcf6fce)
  - Unlabeled drawing and blue print of section of Northern Sector Excavations, MS210.006.00014 (Box data_value_missing_10890b8dfc8b9d0e72ba6dde5bcf6fce)
  - Unlabeled drawing of section of Northern Sector Excavations, MS210.006.00015 (Box data_value_missing_10890b8dfc8b9d0e72ba6dde5bcf6fce)
  - Unlabeled drawing of large section of Northern Sector Excavations, MS210.006.00016 (Box data_value_missing_10890b8dfc8b9d0e72ba6dde5bcf6fce)
  - Unlabeled drawing of Northern Sector Excavations Main Site, MS210.006.00017 (Box data_value_missing_10890b8dfc8b9d0e72ba6dde5bcf6fce)
  - Unlabeled drawing of Northern Sector Excavations Main Site, MS210.006.00018 (Box data_value_missing_10890b8dfc8b9d0e72ba6dde5bcf6fce)
  - Unlabeled drawing of section of Northern Sector Excavations, MS210.006.00019 (Box data_value_missing_a053d47cf4ee696bc75e432ade89bd80)
  - Unlabeled drawing of section of Northern Sector Excavations, MS210.006.00020 (Box data_value_missing_a053d47cf4ee696bc75e432ade89bd80)
  - Unlabeled drawing of section of Northern Sector Excavations, MS210.006.00021 (Box data_value_missing_a053d47cf4ee696bc75e432ade89bd80)
  - Unlabeled drawing of sections of Northern Sector Excavations, MS210.006.00022 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 1)
  - Carthage Northern Sector Canadian Excavations with color markings, MS210.006.00023 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 1)
  - Carthage Northern Sector Canadian Excavations with color markings, MS210.006.00024 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 1)
  - Carthage Northern Sector Canadian Excavations with color markings, MS210.006.00025 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 1)
  - 2CC 2C5 drawing by KMB, 1982; MS210.006.00026 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 1)
  - 2CC 2S50 drawing by KMB, 1982; MS210.006.00027 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 1)
  - Series of drawings, 1979; MS210.006.00028 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 1)
  - Unlableled drawing of Odeon Hill, MS210.006.00029 (Box Large Map Case 1 Drawer 9)
  - Unlableled drawing of Odeon Hill, MS210.006.00030 (Box Large Map Case 1 Drawer 9)
  - unlabeled drawing of street grid, MS210.006.00031 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 1)
  - Drawing of trenches, MS210.006.00032 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 1)
  - Drawing of topography in unlabeled drawing of a section of Northern Sector, MS210.006.00033 (Box data_value_missing_97cfa01f138be565b59549700ce0186c)
  - Drawing of original floor level, MS210.006.00034 (Box data_value_missing_97cfa01f138be565b59549700ce0186c)
  - Drawing of a dog near wall opening, MS210.006.00035 (Box data_value_missing_97cfa01f138be565b59549700ce0186c)
  - Drawing of stairway, MS210.006.00036 (Box data_value_missing_97cfa01f138be565b59549700ce0186c)
  - Mosaic drawing, MS210.006.00037 (Box data_value_missing_dc7ace542b41f32a9f14d9cbd2de2f1e)
  - Unlabeled drawing of section of Northern Sector Excavations, MS210.006.00038 (Box data_value_missing_dc7ace542b41f32a9f14d9cbd2de2f1e)
  - Unlabeled drawing of a wall, MS210.006.00039 (Box data_value_missing_dc7ace542b41f32a9f14d9cbd2de2f1e)
  - Unlabeled drawing of a wall, MS210.006.00040 (Box data_value_missing_dc7ace542b41f32a9f14d9cbd2de2f1e)
  - Unlabeled drawing of a wall, MS210.006.00041 (Box data_value_missing_dc7ace542b41f32a9f14d9cbd2de2f1e)
  - Unlabeled drawing of a wall, MS210.006.00042 (Box data_value_missing_dc7ace542b41f32a9f14d9cbd2de2f1e)
  - Unlabeled drawing of a wall, MS210.006.00043 (Box data_value_missing_dc7ace542b41f32a9f14d9cbd2de2f1e)
  - Unlabeled drawing of a section of a wall, MS210.006.00044 (Box data_value_missing_dc7ace542b41f32a9f14d9cbd2de2f1e)
  - Unlabeled drawing of a section of a wall, MS210.006.00045 (Box data_value_missing_dc7ace542b41f32a9f14d9cbd2de2f1e)
  - Large Scale Tracings for Plans, MS210.006.00046 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 1)
  - Unlabeled drawing of section of Northern Sector Excavations, MS210.006.00047 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 1)
  - Chantier No. 2, MS210.006.00048 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 2)
  - Chantier No. 2, MS210.006.00049 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 2)
  - Drawing for site C. C. 2, MS210.006.00050 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 2)
  - Spike Fragment, MS210.006.00051 (Box data_value_missing_97cfa01f138be565b59549700ce0186c)